Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1 MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: 1960 and Before, 1889-1963; 44 Linear feet (44 boxes)
  - Edit: 1958: America (Offsite-box 422, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1958: Cancer Cigarettes (Offsite-box 422, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1958: Far East: HRL'S "Special" File (Offsite-box 422, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1958: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 422, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1958: Foreign Policy: Max Ways Correspondence (Offsite-box 422, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1958: Foreign Policy: Max Ways Memos (Offsite-box 422, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1958: Latin America (Offsite-box 422, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1958: Law (Offsite-box 422, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1958: Mideast (Offsite-box 422, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1958: Organization (Offsite-box 423)
  - Edit: 1958: Organization [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Edit: 1958: Russia (Offsite-box 423, Folder 2)
  - Edit: 1958: Misc (Offsite-box 423, Folder 3-4)
  - Edit: 1959: America (Offsite-box 423, Folder 5)
  - Edit: 1959: Cancer Cigarette (Offsite-box 423, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1959: Far East (Offsite-box 423, Folder 7)
  - Edit: 1959: Foreign Policy: Max Ways Book "Beyond Survival" (Offsite-box 423, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1959: Latin America: Bolivia (Offsite-box 423, Folder 9)
  - Edit: 1959: Latin America: Cuba (Offsite-box 423, Folder 10-11)
  - Edit: 1959: Latin America: Misc (Offsite-box 423, Folder 12)
  - Edit: 1959: Law (Offsite-box 423, Folder 13)
  - Edit: 1959: Organization (Offsite-box 423, Folder 14)
  - Edit: "Political Theory" (Special Research File for H.R.L.) (Offsite-box 423, Folder 15)
  - Edit: 1959: Russia (Offsite-box 423, Folder 16)
  - Edit: 1959: Space & Missiles (Offsite-box 423, Folder 17)
  - Edit: 1959: Misc (Offsite-box 423, Folder 18)
  - Edit: 1960: America: Jan-March (Offsite-box 423, Folder 19)
  - Edit: 1960: America: April-June (Offsite-box 423, Folder 20)
  - Edit: 1960: America: July-Sept (Offsite-box 423, Folder 21)
  - Edit: 1960: America: Oct-Dec (Offsite-box 423, Folder 22)
  - Edit: 1960: Cancer Cigarette (Offsite-box 423, Folder 23)
  - Edit: 1960: Far East: Japanese Press Incident (Offsite-box 423, Folder 24)
  - Edit: 1960: Far East: Vietnam (Offsite-box 423, Folder 25)
  - Edit: 1960: Far East: Misc (Offsite-box 423, Folder 26)
  - Edit: 1960: Latin America (Offsite-box 423, Folder 27)
  - Edit: 1960: Law (Offsite-box 443, Folder 6)
  - Edit: 1960: Misc (Offsite-box 423, Folder 28)
  - Edit: 1960: Organization (Offsite-box 423, Folder 29-30)
  - Editorial Services: 1941 & Before (Offsite-box 424, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Services: 1942-1950 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 2)
  - Editorial Services: 1951-1960 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 3)
  - Films (Offsite-box 424, Folder 4)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Preface (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Preface [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Misc (Undated Papers) (Offsite-box 424, Folder 6)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Board of Directors Memos (Offsite-box 424, Folder 7)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 424, Folder 8)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Correspondence: 1928- August 1929 (Offsite-box 424, Folder 9)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Correspondence: September-December 1929 (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune, Before Feb, 1930: Correspondence: September-December 1929 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1930: Response to First Issues (Offsite-box 424, Folder 11-12)
  - Fortune: 1930: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1930: Edit: Stories [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1930: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1930: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1931: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 424, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1931: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1931: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1931: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Stories: 12/31, Branch Banking (Offsite-box 424, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1932: Edit: Stories: Housing Series (Offsite-box 424, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1932: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1933: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1933: Edit: Stories: 8/33, International Harvester (Offsite-box 424, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1933: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1933: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 424, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: New Yorker (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: New Yorker [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: Jan-May (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: Jan-May [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: June-Dec (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Misc: June-Dec [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Munitions (Offsite-box 424)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Munitions [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: Du Ponts (Offsite-box 425, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1934: Edit: Stories: 12/34, Illuminated Manuscrips (Offsite-box 425, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1934: Misc (Offsite-box 425, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 4/35, Nervous Breakdown (Offsite-box 425, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 10/35, Hearst (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 10/35, Hearst [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Stories: 11/35, Campbell Soup (Offsite-box 425, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1935: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 425, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1935: Misc (Offsite-box 425, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 1/36-7/36 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 1/36-7/36 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 8/36-12/36 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 8/36-12/36 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 425, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 2/36, Jews in America (Offsite-box 425, Folder 14-15)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 3/36, U.S. Steel (Offsite-box 425, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 3/36, ALF Landon (Offsite-box 425, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 4/36, Twin Cities (Offsite-box 425, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 8/36, Small Town, Rochester (Offsite-box 425, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1936: Edit: Stories: 9/36, Japanese Issue (Offsite-box 425, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1936: Misc (Offsite-box 425, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Meetings (Offsite-box 425, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Hodgins' Respectus (Offsite-box 425, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 1/37-7/37 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 1/37-7/37 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 9/37, Shipping (Offsite-box 425, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 8/37-12/37 (Offsite-box 425)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 8/37-12/37 [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 12/37, University of Chicago (Offsite-box 425, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 1/37, Simmons (Offsite-box 425, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 3/37 Cancer (Offsite-box 425, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 3/37, Background for War: Britain (Offsite-box 425, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 4/37, Aviation Safety (Offsite-box 426, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 4/37, Background for War: Spain (Offsite-box 426, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 5/37, It Happened in Steel (Offsite-box 426, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 5/37, Background for War: Germany (Offsite-box 426, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 6/37, Background for War: France (Offsite-box 426, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 7/37, Background for War: Armaments (Offsite-box 426, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 8/37; Background for War: Russia (Offsite-box 426, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 11/37, Industrial Warfare (Offsite-box 426, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Stories: 11/37, Southern Pacific (Offsite-box 426, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1937: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1937: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Business and Government Editorials (Offsite-box 426, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 2/38, Accident of Birth (Offsite-box 426, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 4/38, Small Town, Oskaloosa (Offsite-box 426, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 1/38-6/38 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 10/38, AMA (Offsite-box 426, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 7/38-12/38 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 19-20)
  - Fortune: 1938: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Business and Government Editorials (Offsite-box 426, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 2/39, Vermont Farm (Offsite-box 426, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 7/39, New York Issue (Offsite-box 426, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 1/39-7/39 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Stories: 8/39-12/39 (Offsite-box 426, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1939: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1939: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Stories: 6/40, Philippines (Offsite-box 426, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Stories: 8/40, Hawaii (Offsite-box 426, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1940: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 32-33)
  - Fortune: 1938: Edit: Stories: 10/38, Mexico (Offsite-box 426, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1940: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 426, Folder 34)
  - Fortune: 1941: Edit: Stories: 3/41, Air Power Issue (Offsite-box 427, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1941: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1941: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1941: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1942: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 1/42-4/42 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 5/42-12/42 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 2/42, American Locomotives (Offsite-box 427, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 2/42, Negroes and War (Offsite-box 427, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1942: Edit: Stories: 8/42, Patent Laws (Offsite-box 427, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Stories: 1/43, Air Navigation (Offsite-box 427, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Stories: 1/43-6/43 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Stories: 7/43-12/43 (Offsite-box 427, Folder 15-16)
  - Fortune: 1943: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1943: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1944: Edit: Stories: 4/44, Japan Issue (Offsite-box 427, Folder 19-20)
  - Fortune: 1944: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 21-22)
  - Fortune: 1944: Misc (Offsite-box 427, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1944: History (Offsite-box 427, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 427, Folder 25-26)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: 2/45, West Coast Issue (Offsite-box 428, Folder 1-2)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: 3/45, Beardsley Ruml (Offsite-box 428, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: 10/45, Sugar (Offsite-box 428, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1945: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1945: Fortnightly [empty] (Offsite-box 428, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1945: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1946: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1946: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 428, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1946: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Stories: 6/47-7/47: Economics (Offsite-box 428, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Stories: 3/47, Coal (Offsite-box 428, Folder 13-14)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1947: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1947: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Directive (Offsite-box 428, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1948: Response to Directive Mailing (Offsite-box 428, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 1/48-2/48 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 20-21)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 3/48-4/48 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 22-23)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 5/48-8/48 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 24-25)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Misc: 9/48-12/48 (Offsite-box 428, Folder 26)
  - Fortune: 1948: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 428, Folder 27)
  - Fortune: 1948: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1949: Edit: Stories: 4/49, Japanese Economic Recovery (Offsite-box 428, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1949: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 428, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1949: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1949: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1950: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1950: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1950: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1950: Edit: Stories: 1/50, Made in France, Portfolio (Offsite-box 429, Folder 6)
  - Fortune: 1951: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 7)
  - Fortune: 1951: Edit: Stories: 2/51, The Permanent Revolution (Offsite-box 429, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1951: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1951: The Tycoon is Dead (Offsite-box 429, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1951: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1952: Edit: Stories: 2/52, Washington Issue (Offsite-box 429, Folder 12)
  - Fortune: 1952: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 13)
  - Fortune: 1952: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1952: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 15)
  - Fortune: 1953: Edit: Stories: 2/53, Russian Issue (Offsite-box 429, Folder 16)
  - Fortune: 1953: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1953: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1953: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1954: Edit: Stories: 5/54, New York Central (Offsite-box 429, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1954: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1954: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1954: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Anniversary Series (Offsite-box 429, Folder 24)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Misc: 1/55-6/55 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 25)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Misc: 7/55-12/55 (Offsite-box 429, Folder 26-27)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 28)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: 12/55, Art Market (Offsite-box 429, Folder 29)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: 2/55, Confident Twenty-Fives (Offsite-box 429, Folder 30)
  - Fortune: 1955: Edit: Stories: 8/55, GSA (Offsite-box 429, Folder 31)
  - Fortune: 1955: Misc (Offsite-box 429, Folder 32)
  - Fortune: 1956: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 1)
  - Fortune: 1956: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 2)
  - Fortune: 1956: Edit: Stories: 3/56, National Security Council (Offsite-box 430, Folder 3)
  - Fortune: 1956: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 4)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 5)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: 2/57 and 7/57, Russia (Offsite-box 430)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: 2/57 and 7/57, Russia [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 430)
  - Fortune: 1957: Edit: Stories: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Fortune: 1957: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 8)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Stories: 8/58, Mc Cone Arrives in Washington (Offsite-box 430, Folder 9)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Stories: 12/58, TV: The Light That Failed (Offsite-box 430, Folder 10)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 11)
  - Fortune: 1958: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 12-13)
  - Fortune: 1958: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 14)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 15-16)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Stories: 1/59 and 7/59, Howard Hughes (Offsite-box 430, Folder 17)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Stories: 12/59, Rostow-Wright Debate (Offsite-box 430, Folder 18)
  - Fortune: 1959: Edit: Stories: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 19)
  - Fortune: 1959: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 20)
  - Fortune: 1960: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 21)
  - Fortune: 1960: Edit: Stories (Offsite-box 430, Folder 22)
  - Fortune: 1960: 30th Anniversary (Offsite-box 430, Folder 23)
  - Fortune: 1960: Misc (Offsite-box 430, Folder 24)
  - FYI [employee newsletter] (Offsite-box 430, Folder 25-26)
  - International (TLI): 1936-1944 (Offsite-box 430, Folder 27)
  - International (TLI): 1945: Jan.-Aug. (Offsite-box 430, Folder 28)
  - International (TLI): 1945: Sept.-Dec. (Offsite-box 430, Folder 29)
  - International (TLI): 1946: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 430-431)
  - International (TLI): 1946: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 431)
  - International (TLI): 1946: July-Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - International (TLI): 1947 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 3)
  - International (TLI): 1948 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 4)
  - International (TLI): 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 5)
  - International (TLI): 1951-1953 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 6)
  - International (TLI): 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 7)
  - International (TLI): 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 8)
  - International (TLI): 1958 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 9)
  - International (TLI): 1959 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 10)
  - International (TLI): 1960 (Offsite-box 431, Folder 11)
  - Legal Department (Offsite-box 431)
  - Legal Department [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1935 and Before: Includes Martin Experiment (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1935 and Before: Includes Martin Experiment [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1936: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 431, Folder 15-16)
  - Life: 1936: June: Prospectus --- Draft #1 ("Dime") (Offsite-box 431, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1936: Prospectus, Draft #2 ("Showbook"): Working Papers (Offsite-box 431, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1936: Names (Proposed) (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1936: Names (Proposed) [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1936: Jan-May (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1936: Jan-May [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1936: June: Misc (Offsite-box 431, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1936: July: Dummy #1 ("This is Dummy") (Offsite-box 431, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1936: July: Prospectus, Draft #2 ("Showbook"): Originals of Final Version (Offsite-box 431, Folder 23-24)
  - Life: 1936: July: Misc (Offsite-box 431)
  - Life: 1936: July: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1936: August (Offsite-box 431-432)
  - Life: 1936: September: Misc (Offsite-box 432, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1936: September: Dummy #2 (Rehearsal) (Offsite-box 432, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1936: October: Ingersoll's Opus (Offsite-box 432, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1936: October: Misc (Offsite-box 432, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1936: November: Outside Comment (Offsite-box 432, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1936: December: Outside Comment (Offsite-box 432, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1936: December: Misc (Offsite-box 432, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1936: November: Misc (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1936: November: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1937: "Coming to Life" (Offsite-box 432, Folder 10-11)
  - Life: 1937: Edit (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1937: Edit [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: Jan.-June (Offsite-box 432, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: July-Dec. (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: July-Dec. [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1937: Publishing: RCA "Listen" Campaign (Offsite-box 432, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: "Birth of a Baby" (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: "Birth of a Baby" [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: Housing Series (Offsite-box 432, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: Misc (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1938: Edit: Misc [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1938: Publishing: CSMA #1 (Offsite-box 432, Folder 23-24)
  - Life: 1938: Publishing (Offsite-box 432)
  - Life: 1938: Publishing [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Commissioned Art Series (Offsite-box 433, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Housing Series (Offsite-box 433, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 433, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1939: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1939: Edit: Contemplated editorial on aid to allies by HRL, never run (Offsite-box 433, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1940: Edit: Housing Series (Offsite-box 433, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1940: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 433, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1940: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1941 and Before: Edit: Corcoran Lawsuit (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1941 and Before: Edit: Corcoran Lawsuit [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 433, Folder 10)
  - Life: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, History of Picture Magazines (Offsite-box 433, Folder 12)
  - Life: 1942 and Before: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Depositions (Offsite-box 433, Folder 13)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (1) (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (1) [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (2) (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Corcoran Legal Case, Miscellaneous (2) [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: "Open Letter" to England, 10/17/42 (Offsite-box 433, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1942: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1942: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1943: Edit (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1943: Edit [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1943: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool (Offsite-box 433, Folder 22)
  - Life: 1943: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: "Dear Gang" Letters (to Photographers) (Offsite-box 433, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1944: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool (Offsite-box 433, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1944: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1944: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1944: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 433)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1945: Edit: Wartime Picture Pool (Offsite-box 433, Folder 30)
  - Life: 1945: Publishing (Offsite-box 433, Folder 31)
  - Life: 1946: Anniversary 10th (Offsite-box 433, Folder 32-33)
  - Life: 1946: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434, Folder 1-2)
  - Life: 1946: Publishing (Offsite-box 434, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1947: Edit: Art (Offsite-box 434, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1947: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434)
  - Life: 1947: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Box R3)
  - Life: 1947: Publishing (Offsite-box 434, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1948: Circulation Budgets (Offsite-box 434, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Art (Offsite-box 434, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1948: Edit: Art and Round Table on Art (Offsite-box 434, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1948: Edit: Organization (Offsite-box 434, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1948: Publishing (Offsite-box 434, Folder 11)
  - Life: 1948: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434, Folder 12)
  - Life: Edit: Roundtable, "Pursuit of Happiness" (Offsite-box 434, Folder 13)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Department Story Seg. to E.K.T. (Offsite-box 434, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: 1949: Edit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 434)